<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>beef on Mostly Harmless Cafe</title>
    <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/tags/beef.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in beef on Mostly Harmless Cafe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:25:22 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/tags/beef/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blue Cheese Burger</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/blue-cheese-burger.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:25:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/blue-cheese-burger.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb ground beef (20%+ fat) hamburger buns jalapeno (sliced, ⅛ inch) yellow onion (sliced as thin as you can) ⅓ cup of blue cheese crumbles if you&amp;rsquo;re using a solid block, cut off enough to stack on a burger about ¼ inch high blackened seasoning buffalo sauce of choice salt &amp;amp; pepper Instructions: On medium heat, toast the inner side of the buns with olive oil. About 2½-3 minutes is usually enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jalapeno Cheddar Burger</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/jalapeno-cheddar-burger.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/jalapeno-cheddar-burger.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (beef): I know that American Cheese isn&amp;rsquo;t very popular with a lot of people but it melts better than most other cheeses so it&amp;rsquo;s good for putting on top of other ingredients.
½ pound ground beef 1 slice of cheddar cheese 1 slice of american cheese (subst. whatever cheese you want) 1 jalapeno (sliced to desired thickness) Ingredients (sauce): This is about enough sauce for 10 burgers so put the difference in a box or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Stroganoff</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/beef-stroganoff.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/beef-stroganoff.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb wide egg noodles (dry) ¼ cup butter (divide into 2) 1½ lbs thin sliced chuck (~¼inch) salt &amp;amp; pepper 1 yellow onion (sliced) 1 lb bella mushrooms (sliced) 4 cloves garlic (minced) ½ cup white wine subst: ½ cup vegetable stock and 1 tbsp white vinegar 2 cups beef stock 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce 3½ tbsp all-purpose flour ½ cup sour cream opt: set aside additional for topping Instructions: Cover meat in salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepperoncini Roast</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/pepperoncini-roast.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/pepperoncini-roast.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 3½-4 lbs chuck roast 1 jar pepperoncinis (capped, kepp juice) 1 8 oz. can tomato sauce (keep jar for water) 1 oz. packet ranch seasoning 1 oz. packet au jus 1 oz. packet beef stew seasoning 4 carrots (split and segmented) 1 yellow onion (diced) Instructions: Preheat oven to 375°F. Season roast generously with salt and pepper on all sides. Let sit for 6 minutes. Put oil in dutch oven on med-high, sear roast, approx.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
