<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mostly Harmless Cafe</title>
    <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mostly Harmless Cafe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:03:56 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aperol Spritz</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/aperol-spritz.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 20:03:56 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/aperol-spritz.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients ice 3 oz. prosecco 3 oz. aperol subst: select 1 oz. club soda 2 olives (garnish) Instructions Add everything in glass, stir to combine. Optional Serve before lunch </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/lasagna.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 09:33:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/lasagna.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 9 lasagna noodles 1 lb ground beef ½ lb ground pork subst: ¼ lb sausage 8 oz mushrooms (sliced) 1 small onion (diced) 1 tsp fennel seeds (ground) 6 oz can of tomato paste 28 oz can of crushed tomatoes 2 cloves of garlic (minced) 2 inch knob of ginger (minced) 15 oz ricotta 1 egg ¼ cup pecorino romano 8 oz mozzarella cheese not pre-shredded, cheaper is better, feel free to add more salt &amp;amp; pepper vegetable oil (for cooking meat) olive oil (for cooking sauce) Instructions Preheat oven to 375F Cook noodles per box instructions (don&amp;rsquo;t forget to salt water).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blue Cheese Burger</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/blue-cheese-burger.html</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:25:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/blue-cheese-burger.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb ground beef (20%+ fat) hamburger buns jalapeno (sliced, ⅛ inch) yellow onion (sliced as thin as you can) ⅓ cup of blue cheese crumbles if you&amp;rsquo;re using a solid block, cut off enough to stack on a burger about ¼ inch high blackened seasoning buffalo sauce of choice salt &amp;amp; pepper Instructions: On medium heat, toast the inner side of the buns with olive oil. About 2½-3 minutes is usually enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curry Aioli</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/curry-aioli.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/curry-aioli.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 2 Tbsp mayonnaise 1 clove of garlic (grated) 1 tsp lemon juice ½ tsp curry powder ¼ tsp salt ¼ tsp pepper Instructions: Combine all ingredients in a bowl and mix. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead&#39;s Fried Rice</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/deads-fried-rice.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/deads-fried-rice.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 1 chicken thigh 1 tbsp shaoxing wine subst: 1 tbsp chicken stock and 1 tsp of lemon juice 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp gochujang 1 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp garlic powder 1 tsp salt Recommended marinade time, 45 min or overnight (optimal)
Ingredients (rice): 1 cup rice (uncooked) chicken stock subst: water ½ onion (diced) 2 inch knob of ginger (minced) 2 eggs (scrambled) 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 clove of garlic (grated) 1 tbsp sambal oelek 1 green onion (thinly sliced) Instructions (chicken): Carve chicken thigh (if necessary), removing bone and skin, and cut into bite size pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Tomato Pasta</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/garlic-tomato-pasta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/garlic-tomato-pasta.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (pasta): 120g pasta (spaghetti, dry) Ingredients (sauce): ¼ cup extra virgin olive oil 3 cloves of garlic 1 anchovy 12 cherry tomatoes (halved) 1 tsp red pepper flakes ½ tsp pepper ½ tsp salt 1 Tbsp lemon juice shredded Pecorino Romano The Pecorino will be garnish so just grate however much you think you&amp;rsquo;ll need. You can also add in some chicken. If you do, marinade it with garlic powder, ground ginger, lemon juice, and salt for around 30-45 minutes, cook, and set aside for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Dead&#39;s Chicken</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-deads-chicken.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-deads-chicken.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 2 chicken thighs 2 tbsp shaoxing wine (subst.: 1 tbsp soy sauce) 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 cloves of garlic (grated) 1 inch knob of ginger (grated) pinch of salt Recommended marinade time: 45 min or overnight (optimal)
Ingredients (dredge): 2 cups of flour 1 cup of corn starch 2 eggs (whites) Ingredients (sauce): 1 tbsp shaoxing wine subst: chinkiang vinegar ½ cup chicken stock 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp mirin optional subst: rice vinegar 3 tbsp sugar 1 tsp msg 3 cloves of garlic (minced) 3 inch knob of ginger (minced) 1 habanero pepper (diced) 1 tbsp cornstarch 1 ½ tbsp vinegar Instructions: Put egg whites in bowl, whisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Tsos Chicken</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-tsos-chicken.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-tsos-chicken.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 2 chicken thighs 2 Tbsp Shaoxing Wine 1 Tbsp soy sauce 2 cloves of garlic (grated) 1 inch knob of ginger (grated) pinch of salt Recommended marinade time, 45 min or overnight (optimal)
Ingredients (sauce): 1 Tbsp Shaoxing Wine ½ cup chicken stock 3 Tbsp soy sauce 3 Tbsp sugar 4 cloves of garlic (minced) 2 inch knob of ginger (minced) 1 tsp chili flakes 5 dried chili peppers 1 Tbsp cornstarch 1 ½ Tbsp vinegar Instructions: Dredge chicken in a 1:1 mix of cornstarch and flour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hot Chocolate</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/hot-chocolate.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/hot-chocolate.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 ½ cups whole milk 4 oz finely chopped cocoa (usally one square, 100% cocoa) 1 ½ Tbsp sugar 1 Tbsp cocoa powder 1 Tbsp cornstarch Instructions: Put chopped cocoa and a splash of milk into pot on med heat, heat until cocoa has melted. Add sugar and cocoa powder. In separate bowl, mix cornstarch with splash of milk (making a slurry). Stream in slurry, mix until consistent and thickened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Irish Car Bomb</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/irish-car-bomb.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/irish-car-bomb.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 pint Irish stout (personal: Guiness) ½ oz Irish cream ¼ oz coffee liqeur ¼ oz Irish whiskey (personal: Jameson) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jalapeno Cheddar Burger</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/jalapeno-cheddar-burger.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/jalapeno-cheddar-burger.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (beef): I know that American Cheese isn&amp;rsquo;t very popular with a lot of people but it melts better than most other cheeses so it&amp;rsquo;s good for putting on top of other ingredients.
½ pound ground beef 1 slice of cheddar cheese 1 slice of american cheese (subst. whatever cheese you want) 1 jalapeno (sliced to desired thickness) Ingredients (sauce): This is about enough sauce for 10 burgers so put the difference in a box or something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Wafu Pasta</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/japanese-wafu-pasta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/japanese-wafu-pasta.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 1 lb spaghetti ¼ cup extra-virgin olive oil 8 Tbsp unsalted butter 4 cloves of garlic ¼ tsp salt 15 cranks of fresh cracked black pepper 1 lb shiitake mushrooms ¼ cup soy sauce 2 scallions (garnish) Instructions: Boil pasta for recommended time, set aside when done, reserving at least ½ cup of pasta water. In skillet on medium heat add olive oil with 4 Tbsp of butter. Once butter melts, add garlic and mushrooms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pancakes</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/pancakes.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/pancakes.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 ½ cups milk 1 egg ¼ cup sugar 1 tsp salt ¼ tsp baking soda 1 Tbsp baking powder 2 Tbsp melted butter Instructions: Pour onto medium heat pan. Flip when bubbles appear on top </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penne Alla Vodka</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/penne-alla-vodka.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/penne-alla-vodka.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb penne pasta ½ Tbsp extra virgin olive oil 100 g pancetta (can use bacon) 1 shallot (minced) 3 cups (2 cans) crushed tomatoes ⅓ cup heavy cream ⅓ cup vodka Instructions: Go ahead and make the pasta before starting the sauce and reserve ¼ cup of the resulting pasta water.
Add olive oil to pan on medium heat. Add pancetta/bacon, let simmer until all the grease has been sweated out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phisch&#39;s BBQ Sauce</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/phisch-bbq-sauce.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/phisch-bbq-sauce.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 cup ketchup 1 shallot (finely diced) subst: red onions 1 clove garlic (finely diced) 1 inch ginger (finely diced) 1 tbsp sunflower oil 1 tsp chili flakes 1½ tbsp. brown sugar 3 tsp smoked paprika 1½ tbsp. apple cider vinegar subst: red wine vinegar 1 tsp worchestorshire sauce 2 tbsp dark soy sauce black pepper salt Instructions: Add shallots, garlic, ginger, sunflower oil, and chili flakes to pan on medium heat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti and Meatballs</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/spaghetti-and-meatballs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/spaghetti-and-meatballs.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (meatballs) ¼ lb ham (minced) 1 lb ground beef 1 tsp ground fennel seeds 1 ¾ tsp sea salt 3 cloves garlic ¼ cup Pecorino Romano (fine shredded) blackpepper (from the hip) ½ cup panko 1 whole egg Ingredients (sauce): ¼ cup extra virgin olive oil 4 cloves garlic (thinly sliced) 1 tsp red pepper flakes t tsp salt 1 can (28 oz.) crushed tomatoes 1 bunch of basil You can use 2 cans of crushed tomatoes if you like a lot of sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Wine Sauce</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/white-wine-sauce.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/white-wine-sauce.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (pasta, chicken, and tomatoes): 1 lb pasta 300 g chicken thighs (cut into bite-size pieces) 1 package of cherry tomatoes (halved) ½ tsp salt ¼ tsp pepper Ingredients (sauce): 3 cloves of garlic (minced) ¼ cup extra virgin olive oil 5 Tbsp butter (unsalted) ½ tsp crushed red pepper 1 tsp salt ½ tsp ground black pepper ½ cup white wine (your choice thereof) Instructions (chicken and tomatoes): If you&amp;rsquo;re having this with pasta, go ahead and cook that, chill with water, and set to the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Stroganoff</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/beef-stroganoff.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/beef-stroganoff.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb wide egg noodles (dry) ¼ cup butter (divide into 2) 1½ lbs thin sliced chuck (~¼inch) salt &amp;amp; pepper 1 yellow onion (sliced) 1 lb bella mushrooms (sliced) 4 cloves garlic (minced) ½ cup white wine subst: ½ cup vegetable stock and 1 tbsp white vinegar 2 cups beef stock 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce 3½ tbsp all-purpose flour ½ cup sour cream opt: set aside additional for topping Instructions: Cover meat in salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Chicken Dip</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/buffalo-chicken-dip.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/buffalo-chicken-dip.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 2 cups shredded chicken 8 oz cream cheese (softened) ½ cup Frank&amp;rsquo;s Red Hot ½ cup ranch 1 block (roughly 6 oz) cheddar cheese (freshly grated) ½ cup blue cheese crumbles Instructions (chicken): Bring water to simmer. Place chicken in water, cover with lid, and leave for 45 minutes. Remove chicken, carve the meat, and shred using whatever works. Instructions (dip): Mix together cream cheese, hot sauce, and ranch. Mix in chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Adobo</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chicken-adobo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chicken-adobo.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 4 lbs chicken Bone in, with skin.
Can be pretty much any part of the chicken. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to have diversity but if only given one choice, chicken thighs work best.
Ingredients (sauce): 20 cloves of garlic (minced) 1 Tbsp black peppercorns crack of fresh ground black pepper 3 Tbsp palm sugar (can use brown sugar) 1 ¼ cup rice vinegar ½ cup soy sauce ¼ cup dark soy sauce ½ cup water Instructions: Marinade chicken for two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Marinade</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chicken-marinade.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chicken-marinade.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 Cup Soy sauce ¼ Cup Worchestorshire sauce ¼ Cup Brown Sugar 3 cloves of garlic (minced) Instructions: Throw all the chicken in a ziplock bag with the marinade, store in fridge, and use as needed. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chow Mein</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chow-mein.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chow-mein.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (noodles): 400g egg noodles 2 chicken breasts (scored and chopped into bite-sized pieces) feel free to marinade 2 green onions (segmented) 1 carror (julienne) 3½ cups cabbage (about half of one head) 7 cloves of garlic (minced) 1 cup bean sprouts 2 Tbsp water Ingredients (sauce): 1½ Tbsp rice vinegar 2½ Tbsp soy sauce 2 Tbsp oyster sauce subst: hoisin sauce 3 tsp sesame oil 2 tsp cornstarch Instructions: Cook chicken to completion in wok, remove, and set to the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pepperoncini Roast</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/pepperoncini-roast.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/pepperoncini-roast.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 3½-4 lbs chuck roast 1 jar pepperoncinis (capped, kepp juice) 1 8 oz. can tomato sauce (keep jar for water) 1 oz. packet ranch seasoning 1 oz. packet au jus 1 oz. packet beef stew seasoning 4 carrots (split and segmented) 1 yellow onion (diced) Instructions: Preheat oven to 375°F. Season roast generously with salt and pepper on all sides. Let sit for 6 minutes. Put oil in dutch oven on med-high, sear roast, approx.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
