<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>chicken on Mostly Harmless Cafe</title>
    <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/tags/chicken.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in chicken on Mostly Harmless Cafe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:47:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/tags/chicken/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chicken</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/chicken.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 09:47:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/chicken.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead&#39;s Fried Rice</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/deads-fried-rice.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/deads-fried-rice.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 1 chicken thigh 1 tbsp shaoxing wine subst: 1 tbsp chicken stock and 1 tsp of lemon juice 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp gochujang 1 tsp ground ginger 1 tsp garlic powder 1 tsp salt Recommended marinade time, 45 min or overnight (optimal)
Ingredients (rice): 1 cup rice (uncooked) chicken stock subst: water ½ onion (diced) 2 inch knob of ginger (minced) 2 eggs (scrambled) 1 tbsp soy sauce 1 clove of garlic (grated) 1 tbsp sambal oelek 1 green onion (thinly sliced) Instructions (chicken): Carve chicken thigh (if necessary), removing bone and skin, and cut into bite size pieces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Dead&#39;s Chicken</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-deads-chicken.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-deads-chicken.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 2 chicken thighs 2 tbsp shaoxing wine (subst.: 1 tbsp soy sauce) 1 tbsp soy sauce 2 cloves of garlic (grated) 1 inch knob of ginger (grated) pinch of salt Recommended marinade time: 45 min or overnight (optimal)
Ingredients (dredge): 2 cups of flour 1 cup of corn starch 2 eggs (whites) Ingredients (sauce): 1 tbsp shaoxing wine subst: chinkiang vinegar ½ cup chicken stock 3 tbsp soy sauce 1 tbsp mirin optional subst: rice vinegar 3 tbsp sugar 1 tsp msg 3 cloves of garlic (minced) 3 inch knob of ginger (minced) 1 habanero pepper (diced) 1 tbsp cornstarch 1 ½ tbsp vinegar Instructions: Put egg whites in bowl, whisk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Tsos Chicken</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-tsos-chicken.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/general-tsos-chicken.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 2 chicken thighs 2 Tbsp Shaoxing Wine 1 Tbsp soy sauce 2 cloves of garlic (grated) 1 inch knob of ginger (grated) pinch of salt Recommended marinade time, 45 min or overnight (optimal)
Ingredients (sauce): 1 Tbsp Shaoxing Wine ½ cup chicken stock 3 Tbsp soy sauce 3 Tbsp sugar 4 cloves of garlic (minced) 2 inch knob of ginger (minced) 1 tsp chili flakes 5 dried chili peppers 1 Tbsp cornstarch 1 ½ Tbsp vinegar Instructions: Dredge chicken in a 1:1 mix of cornstarch and flour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalo Chicken Dip</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/buffalo-chicken-dip.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/buffalo-chicken-dip.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 2 cups shredded chicken 8 oz cream cheese (softened) ½ cup Frank&amp;rsquo;s Red Hot ½ cup ranch 1 block (roughly 6 oz) cheddar cheese (freshly grated) ½ cup blue cheese crumbles Instructions (chicken): Bring water to simmer. Place chicken in water, cover with lid, and leave for 45 minutes. Remove chicken, carve the meat, and shred using whatever works. Instructions (dip): Mix together cream cheese, hot sauce, and ranch. Mix in chicken.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chicken Adobo</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chicken-adobo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/chicken-adobo.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (chicken): 4 lbs chicken Bone in, with skin.
Can be pretty much any part of the chicken. It&amp;rsquo;s nice to have diversity but if only given one choice, chicken thighs work best.
Ingredients (sauce): 20 cloves of garlic (minced) 1 Tbsp black peppercorns crack of fresh ground black pepper 3 Tbsp palm sugar (can use brown sugar) 1 ¼ cup rice vinegar ½ cup soy sauce ¼ cup dark soy sauce ½ cup water Instructions: Marinade chicken for two hours.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
