<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pasta on Mostly Harmless Cafe</title>
    <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/tags/pasta.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in pasta on Mostly Harmless Cafe</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 09:33:07 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/tags/pasta/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lasagna</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/lasagna.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 09:33:07 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/lasagna.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients 9 lasagna noodles 1 lb ground beef ½ lb ground pork subst: ¼ lb sausage 8 oz mushrooms (sliced) 1 small onion (diced) 1 tsp fennel seeds (ground) 6 oz can of tomato paste 28 oz can of crushed tomatoes 2 cloves of garlic (minced) 2 inch knob of ginger (minced) 15 oz ricotta 1 egg ¼ cup pecorino romano 8 oz mozzarella cheese not pre-shredded, cheaper is better, feel free to add more salt &amp;amp; pepper vegetable oil (for cooking meat) olive oil (for cooking sauce) Instructions Preheat oven to 375F Cook noodles per box instructions (don&amp;rsquo;t forget to salt water).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garlic Tomato Pasta</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/garlic-tomato-pasta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/garlic-tomato-pasta.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (pasta): 120g pasta (spaghetti, dry) Ingredients (sauce): ¼ cup extra virgin olive oil 3 cloves of garlic 1 anchovy 12 cherry tomatoes (halved) 1 tsp red pepper flakes ½ tsp pepper ½ tsp salt 1 Tbsp lemon juice shredded Pecorino Romano The Pecorino will be garnish so just grate however much you think you&amp;rsquo;ll need. You can also add in some chicken. If you do, marinade it with garlic powder, ground ginger, lemon juice, and salt for around 30-45 minutes, cook, and set aside for later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penne Alla Vodka</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/penne-alla-vodka.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/penne-alla-vodka.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb penne pasta ½ Tbsp extra virgin olive oil 100 g pancetta (can use bacon) 1 shallot (minced) 3 cups (2 cans) crushed tomatoes ⅓ cup heavy cream ⅓ cup vodka Instructions: Go ahead and make the pasta before starting the sauce and reserve ¼ cup of the resulting pasta water.
Add olive oil to pan on medium heat. Add pancetta/bacon, let simmer until all the grease has been sweated out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spaghetti and Meatballs</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/spaghetti-and-meatballs.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/spaghetti-and-meatballs.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (meatballs) ¼ lb ham (minced) 1 lb ground beef 1 tsp ground fennel seeds 1 ¾ tsp sea salt 3 cloves garlic ¼ cup Pecorino Romano (fine shredded) blackpepper (from the hip) ½ cup panko 1 whole egg Ingredients (sauce): ¼ cup extra virgin olive oil 4 cloves garlic (thinly sliced) 1 tsp red pepper flakes t tsp salt 1 can (28 oz.) crushed tomatoes 1 bunch of basil You can use 2 cans of crushed tomatoes if you like a lot of sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>White Wine Sauce</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/white-wine-sauce.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/white-wine-sauce.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients (pasta, chicken, and tomatoes): 1 lb pasta 300 g chicken thighs (cut into bite-size pieces) 1 package of cherry tomatoes (halved) ½ tsp salt ¼ tsp pepper Ingredients (sauce): 3 cloves of garlic (minced) ¼ cup extra virgin olive oil 5 Tbsp butter (unsalted) ½ tsp crushed red pepper 1 tsp salt ½ tsp ground black pepper ½ cup white wine (your choice thereof) Instructions (chicken and tomatoes): If you&amp;rsquo;re having this with pasta, go ahead and cook that, chill with water, and set to the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beef Stroganoff</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/beef-stroganoff.html</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jun 2023 16:39:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/posts/beef-stroganoff.html</guid>
      <description>Ingredients: 1 lb wide egg noodles (dry) ¼ cup butter (divide into 2) 1½ lbs thin sliced chuck (~¼inch) salt &amp;amp; pepper 1 yellow onion (sliced) 1 lb bella mushrooms (sliced) 4 cloves garlic (minced) ½ cup white wine subst: ½ cup vegetable stock and 1 tbsp white vinegar 2 cups beef stock 1 tbsp worcestershire sauce 3½ tbsp all-purpose flour ½ cup sour cream opt: set aside additional for topping Instructions: Cover meat in salt and pepper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pasta</title>
      <link>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/pasta.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 18:00:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://testing.mostlyharmless.cafe/pasta.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
